hello everyone and welcome again to
大家好，欢迎再次
floss our course on open source software
我们 floss 的开源软件课程
in this session we will look at the
参加本次会议的开源软件课程，我们将研究
processes and practices of open source
开源项目社区的流程和实践，
project communities and for this we will
为此我们将
look at the structure of projects the
研究项目的结构
roles people play in the career path
人们在职业道路上扮演的角色
they can have and then we look at what I
他们可以有，然后我们看看我
call the three four five model of open
称之为开放
communities or project communities which
社区或项目社区的三四五模式，它们
are the principles of three principles
是本课程开头提到
of open collaboration for practices of
的开放式协作交流实践的三个原则
communication and five stages of open
和开源志愿服务的五个阶段的原则
source volunteering as mentioned in the
beginning of this course open source is
highly innovative meaning in this case
在这种情况下
on the domain or the aspects of process
，源在领域或流程创新的方面具有高度创新的含义，
innovation open source community
开源社区
processes are quite different from what
流程与
we are used to say from within companies
我们过去在公司内部所说的完全不同，
so open source has brought us new
因此开源为我们带来了新
processes of collaboration and here
的协作流程，
specifically of community-based project
特别是社区 - 基于项目
collaboration it helps to contrast this
协作，它有助于对比这一点
to make sure we understand how this is
，以确保我们了解这是如何
different and we are deepen that
不同的 t，我们加深了
understanding about how it's different
对公司内部发生的事情在第一步中的不同之处的理解，
in the first step for what happens
within firms so within a firm you have a
因此在公司内部你有一个
project structure such that the firm a
项目结构，这样
company owns the project and the
公司拥有项目和
intellectual property with it and also
知识产权，
you also can fully determine any project
你也可以完全 确定任何项目的
structures its the firm or the CEO of
结构 它的公司或公司的 CEO
the firm ultimately who determines how
最终决定
things work inside an open source
开源项目或开源项目内部的运作
project or an open source project it's
the community which holds the software
by way of a license and a community
方式 是通过许可证持有软件的
which decides on how the project is
社区和决定项目如何运作的社区
conducted and the community is not a
进行并且社区不是
legal entity so it is
法律实体，因此是
group of people that collaborates and
一群人协作并
forwar a decision-making and all of that
推动决策制定，所有这些
is the result of sort of consensus
都是建立共识过程的结果
building process and that's very
，这与公司非常
different from companies so in this
不同，因此在本
session we will be talking about
次会议中，我们将
community open source projects again
再次谈论社区开源
projects owned and run by a community
项目 由社区拥有和运营的项目
I'm saying this because later it will
我这么说是因为以后会变得很
become become apparent that open source
明显 源代码
could also not be community oriented so
也可能不是面向社区的，因此
we will distinguish between commercial
我们将区分商业
and community open source it's not quite
和社区开源它不太
accurate or say commercial here but
准确或在这里说商业但
we'll see the differences in later
我们将在以后的会议中看到差异，
sessions but for that purpose or
但出于此目的或
commercial open source projects are
商业开源项目
those controlled by a company and
是由公司控制的项目 并且
there's that one legal entity
有一个法律实体
controlling the software and the project
控制该软件和该项目
an example suffering the other Sugar CRM
一个示例遭受其他
software for customer relationship
用于客户关系
management or the
管理的 Sugar CRM 软件或由 Red Hat 控制的
Linux distribution Red Hat Enterprise
Linux 发行版 Red Hat Enterprise
Linux distribution which is controlled
Linux 发行版，而不是
by Red Hat as opposed to that there are
community software software's projects
社区软件软件的项目，
like the Linux kernel which is solely
例如 完全基于社区的 Linux 内核
community based or the Debian
或 Debian
distribution also I made a distinction
发行版 我在这里已经做了区分
here already in that there can be very
，因为开源项目的结构可能有非常
different types of open-source projects
不同的类型
by structure and I made a distinction
，我在
here between single components or
这里对单个组件或
applications or whole distributions
应用程序或整个发行版进行了区分
where the community puts together some
，其中 社区汇集
of the all of the many different pieces
了所有的一些 许多不同的部分，
and makes it work together that's the
并使其协同工作，这就是
distribution alright so let's talk now
分布，所以现在让我们
about how open source project
谈谈开源项目
communities function here is a classic
社区如何在这里运作，这
model of different roles that people
是人们扮演的不同角色的经典模型，
play and also what power this gives them
以及这在项目中赋予他们什么权力，
within a project so you could have
所以你可以
someone simply
简单地拥有某人
reading up on a project number one here
using the software but not saying
使用该软件阅读此处的第一个项目，但不说
anything being a passive user then
任何内容作为被动用户然后
perhaps becoming a back reporter by
可能通过
reporting a back maybe has a developer
报告背部而成为背部记者可能会让开发人员
becoming a back fixer then making the
成为背部修复者，然后
occasional episodic or peripheral
contribution as a peripheral developer
作为外围开发人员偶尔做出偶发性或外围贡献
here or becoming an active regular
或成为积极的定期
contributor finally becoming a comment
贡献者最终成为评论
or a project leader this model is called
或项目负责人此模型
the onion model because it's not only a
称为洋葱模型，因为它不仅是
set of roles that people can play but it
人们可以扮演的一组角色，而且
also suggests that there's a succession
还表明这里正在进行继任
or a project immigration model going on
或项目移民模型，
here but you have to take on these roles
但是 你必须承担这些角色
and steps now I've color-coded these
和步骤现在我已经对这些
rings or of the onion if you will
环或洋葱进行了颜色编码，如果你 将
already into three main categories which
已经分为三个主要类别，这
is a simplification but a good enough
是一种简化，但已经足够好了
one where we can see that we distinguish
between people using the software people
are contributing to the software and
people leading the software also being
called committer very big project so
that actually is simplifying leads to
导致某人
the basic career path that someone can
have in an open-source project they
在开源项目中可以拥有的基本职业道路他们
start out as a user they might make a
以用户身份开始，他们可能
contribution to the project and that if
为项目做出贡献，如果
that contribution gets accepted they
该贡献被接受，他们
implicitly promoted to become a
隐含地
contributor to that project can call
提升为该项目的贡献者可以称
themselves that sometimes also simply
自己 有时也简称
called
为
developer and if they do so regularly
开发人员，如果他们定期
and in a sustained and quality way then
并以持续和优质的方式这样做，那么
they might be appointed by the existing
他们可能会被现有
committees and project leaders to become
委员会和项目负责人任命为项目
a core member or committee of the
的核心成员或委员会
project and that is usually an explicit
，这通常是委员会的明确
promotion the committee is someone who
晋升 是
has changed rights to the software
更改了软件
project and the contributor does not
项目权利且贡献者
have changed rights so a contributor
没有权限的人 获得了权利，因此贡献者
submits two core memos
提交了两个核心备忘录
committers and he suggested change what
提交者，他建议更改
gets reviewed and put into action
被审查的内容并付诸行动，
meaning the code repository by the
这意味着提交者的代码存储库
committer only if it's considered a good
只有在它被认为是好的
contribution so contributors depend on
贡献时，所以贡献者依赖于
committees and as implied review process
委员会，并且作为隐含的审查过程
which is also a critical part of the
，这也是一个关键 作为
Quality Assurance and open source
质量保证和开源
projects everyone can become a
项目的一部分，每个人都可以
contributor by simply making a
通过简单的
contribution becoming a committer is a
贡献成为贡献者 成为提交者是一个
much more important event and while you
更重要的事件，而当你
implicitly become a contributor or
隐含地成为贡献者或
becoming a committer is typically
成为提交者时，通常
something that will be announced was
会被宣布为
quite something far on the mailing lists
相当远的事情 在项目的邮件
of the project or whatever way the
列表或项目沟通的任何方式上，
project communicates committees are
委员会很
important because they lead the
重要，因为他们领导
direction of the project there may be a
项目的方向，可能有一个
dedicated project leader or it may be a
专门的项目负责人，或者可能
circle of our group of equal peers that
是我们一群平等的同行，他们
are commuters and consensually lead the
是通勤者并自愿领导
project all of that are various variants
项目所有这些都是各种变体
fountain open source projects now this
喷泉开源项目 现在这
is the basic simplified model also the
是基本的简化模型，也是
onion model but the emergence of open
洋葱模型，但是
source software foundations has led to a
开源软件基金会的出现导致了
more elaborate one so after this basic
一个更复杂的模型，所以在这个基本
career you can have extended or software
职业之后，你可以扩展或者软件
developers can have an extended of them
开发人员可以扩展他们的
sauce career well the project's now part
职业生涯，项目现在
of an open source foundation are managed
开源基金会的一部分
ultimately by or governed are governed
最终
by the open source foundation and its
由开源基金会及其
roots so the open source foundations
根源管理或管理，因此开源
have set up project management committee
基金会设立了项目管理委员会
membership so as a project management
成员资格，因此作为一个项目管理
committee which has members and a leader
委员会，有成员和领导者
and these and the pmc in the project
，这些和 项目
management committee is responsible for
管理委员会
eternity managing the direction of a
中的 pmc 负责永久管理
patek a component or open source project
百达翡丽组件或开源项目的方向
this goes beyond what a committed us who
这超出了
has right rights change
rights to the court repository or
对法院存储库或
relevant artifacts this is really now
相关工件具有正确权利更改权利的承诺我们现在实际上是
about the strategic leadership of some
关于战略领导 一些
open source project and in fact the
开源项目，事实上
reasons why open source foundations
开源基金会
exist and we'll see that in a later
存在的原因 我们将在稍后的
session is to make economically
会议上看到，使经济上
important open source projects long term
重要的开源项目长期
viable to give them a home to make them
可行，为它们提供一个可持续发展的家园，
sustainable but an open source
但是开源
foundation can host many projects of
基金会可以托管许多具有
high economic significance and so
高度经济意义的项目，
there's usually one step more possible
因此通常还有一步 可能
beyond being the leader of project
超越成为项目管理委员会的领导者，
management committee that would only be
这将是
one project one component and you could
一个项目的一个组成部分，您可以
become a director or a member of the
成为基金会的董事或成员
foundation the different stages of how
natural people can become members of a
自然人如何成为
foundation and exert influence beyond a
基金会成员并在单个项目之外施加影响的不同阶段
single project that they are on so
他们在，所以
that's the extended career path what it
这就是扩展的职业道路，这
means for software developers and in
对软件开发人员意味着什么，
terms of the career we will also look at
就职业而言，我们还将
a later session on neighbor economics so
关注稍后关于邻居经济学的会议，所以
this is now an extension of the onion
现在这是洋葱模型的扩展，
model which did not include anything
它不包括任何
about a career beyond to singer project
关于职业的内容 超越歌手项目
as illustrated here a career as part of
，如此处所示，作为
an open source foundation and as
开源基金会的一部分，作为开源基金会的一部分，
indicated open source foundation saw the
开源基金会看到了
home for the economically important open
经济上重要的
source projects that is the platforms
开源项目的所在地，这
that we all build on here you can see
是我们所有人都建立的平台在这里你可以
the full path it's really a six step if
看到完整的路径如果
you will
你要
six stages or six step career model
六个阶段或六步职业模型，这实际上是一个六步
usually developers can't jump any of
通常开发人员不能跳过任何
these steps they take them one after
这些步骤他们 把它们一个接
another now beyond this career we have
一个地拿走，现在超越这个职业，我们
to look at how people work with each
必须看看人们如何相互合作
other and set open source projects and
并设置开源项目，
many projects have found ways of
许多项目已经找到了
describing it perhaps the most prominent
描述它的方法，也许最突出的
one is the Apache way a codification one
一种是 Apache 方式，一个
word hope of
词希望
how the Apache Software Foundation rocks
如何 Apache Software Foundation 非常棒
and how its project work if you go to
，以及它的项目是如何运作的
the website you will find this as the
description of the Apache way that it's
got to be collaborative software
development that they are friendly to
commercial use of the software they
develop high quality security etc so
等等，所以
it's a little bit of it's important
它有点重要的
criteria but so it's a little bit of a
标准，但它有点像
laundry list here is another way of
洗衣单，这是另一种
looking at it this is the interpretation
看待它的方式，这就是解释
or explanation of the Apache way by one
或其中
of its members shane crew and he tried
一位成员 Shane 工作人员
to explain the apache way using these
对 Apache 方式的解释，他试图使用所提供的这
four five six aspects offered and while
四个五个六个方面来解释 Apache 方式，虽然
helpful to mention all of this it's not
有助于提及所有这些，但它并不是
really practical and that it guides you
真正实用的，它引导你
and to my academic mind it's also again
和我的学术思想 这
a little bit of a laundry list so these
也是一个小清单，所以这些
things that simply don't belong in the
东西根本不属于
same category yeah so categorical for
同一类别，是的，因为
that reason uh I developed this simple
这个原因，所以很明确，嗯，我开发了这个简单的
three four five model of open project
三四五开放项目
communities where we characterize open
社区模型，我们在其中描述开放
projects and the communities using the
项目和社区 使用
three principles of open collaboration
开放式协作的三个原则
the four practices of communication and
沟通的四个实践和
the five stages of project volunteering
项目志愿服务的五个阶段
it's also a simplification but it's easy
这也是一个简化但很
to remember so then the three principles
容易记住
of open Kellogg collaboration already
的开放式 Kellogg 协作的三个原则，
mentioned in earlier lectures are that
在前面的讲座中已经提到过，
collaboration is egalitarian
协作是平等的
meritocratic and self-organizing here
精英和自我 - 在这里组织
you can see it compared to traditional
你可以看到它与
work typically inside companies well
通常在公司内部的传统工作
traditional work is hierarchical and
相比 理想的工作是分层的，
hence you're somewhere in the hierarchy
因此您处于分层结构中的某个位置，
and that a net determines what you can
并且网络决定了您可以
see a modular access to open
看到的内容 模块化访问开放式
collaboration is egalitarian it does not
协作是平等主义的 它不
exclude anyone anyone can
排除任何人都可以
contribute we are all on equal footing
做出贡献 我们都是平等的
and will not be a priori are excluded
，不会是先验 被排除
from project projects decision-making in
在项目项目之外
companies is usually status oriented
公司的决策通常是以地位为导向的，
with higher status of winning who gets
具有更高的获胜地位 谁
to make a decision and in open sauce its
可以做出决定，并且公开地说，它的
decisions are based on the merits of the
决定是基于论点的优点，这
argument
meaning the better argument ultimately
意味着如果不是这样，更好的论点最终会
wins if that was not the case people
获胜 如果人们
would leave the project because they
会离开这个项目，因为他们
feel that they are not taken serious
觉得他们没有被认真对待，
meritocracy is also what the Apache
精英管理也是 Apache
Software Foundation says it is based on
软件基金会所说的，
here I frame it a bit more narrowly as
这里我把它作为一个更狭隘的框架，作为
the key of how decisions are made or in
决策的关键，或者作为
companies then as part of a hierarchy
公司的一部分 等级制度中的
not only do you do you are you limited
你 不仅你做 你
in what you can see you are also priests
在你能看到的东西上受到限制 你也是牧师
in a prescribed situation occur tasks
在规定的情况下 发生
assigned you get allocated to a project
分配的任务 你得到所有 位于一个项目
there is no choice for you or process to
中，
follow as you develop software now an
当您开发软件时，您或流程别无选择 现在一个
open collaboration projects that is
开放的协作项目是
different because these are self
不同的，因为这些是自
organizing projects people choose the
组织项目 人们选择
processes choose their project they self
流程 选择他们自组织的项目
organize that is quite the different
，这
stark difference to companies who want
完全不同 希望
developers to be more like cogs and a
开发人员更像齿轮和
machine so that no project depends too
机器的公司，以便没有项目
much on a particular person open
过于依赖特定的人开放
collaboration projects or source
协作项目或源
projects try to work with the strength
项目尝试
of individual people such that they can
利用个人的力量，以便他们可以
get the most out of those who are
从那些
willing to contribute to a project so we
愿意为一个项目做出贡献，所以我们
have these three principles of
有这三个
egalitarian everyone can contribute an
平等主义原则每个人都可以贡献一个
hour to critique decisions are based on
小时来批评决定是基于
the merits of the argument and
论点和
self-organization people organize and
自组织的优点人们组织和
determine their own processes which
确定他们自己的过程，这
really make open-source projects take it
真正让开源项目接受它
the way they do and the reason why I'm
他们这样做的方式以及为什么我
not giving you here as a process or a
不把你作为一个过程或开源作品在这里给你的原因
works
of open-source projects is because there
项目是因为
is no such thing the best we can do is
没有这样的事情我们能做的最好的就是
come up with these principles from our
从我们
analysis of open source projects to tell
对开源项目的分析中拿出这些原则来
everyone tell you how these are similar
告诉大家这些原则有
and what makes the category of open
什么相似之处以及是什么让
source software projects in addition to
开源软件项目的类别除了
collaboration or collaboration is a
协作或 协作是
necessity based on communication which
基于沟通的必要性，
in the case of open source projects has
在开源项目的情况下，必须
to be open communication and it's only
good open communication if that
是开放式沟通，如果该
communication is public not hidden
沟通是公开的而不是
behind doors it's written typically by
隐藏在门后，它通常是通过
email or sometimes also in forums and
电子邮件或有时也在论坛中编写的，并且
it's complete so you're not hiding
它是完整的，所以你 '没有隐藏
anything because that public written
任何东西，因为公开的书面
communication has to be the complete
交流必须是相关内容的完整
record of what's of relevance and if
记录，如果
it's not been written down in email and
它没有在电子邮件中写下来并
made public it has not been said that's
公开，那就没有说这
how the saying goes
就是俗话说的那样
and then finally it will always get
，然后最后它总是会被
archived so this is also in stark
存档 所以这也
contrast to how companies work because
与公司的运作方式形成鲜明对比，因为
first of all in companies communication
首先在公司中，沟通
is not public it's behind the company
是不公开的 在公司
doors and sometimes locked down within a
门后，有时被锁定在一个
project often it's not written because
项目中，通常没有写出来，因为
nobody wants to be exposed to what they
没有人愿意接触他们
have said in the past because they might
过去所说的话，因为他们可能
want to change their opinion it's not
想
often not complete maybe hidden agendas
and suddenly it's not archived because
改变自己的看法 因为
again people don't want to be on to have
再一次，如果人们不得不改变他们的观点，人们又不想
a fire and have their feet held to fire
着火，也不想让他们的脚
if they have to change their opinion
anyway so let's walk through that a
着火，所以让我们
little bit what it means for open source
稍微了解一下这对开源项目意味着什么，
projects so public communication is
所以公共交流就是
communication that's visible to everyone
交流 每个人都可以看到
and thereby it creates trust and
，从而建立信任和
credibility so everyone can draw and
可信度，所以每个人都可以画画，
everyone can participate and so you
每个人都可以参与，所以你
usually do that on mailing lists your
通常在邮件列表上这样做你的
void private emails
无效私人电子邮件
certainly don't use the phone etc if you
当然不要使用电话等如果你
have to do something in private
必须私下做某事，
you typically summarize it then and put
你通常会总结 然后将
it in writing to the mailing list
其以书面形式写入邮件列表
written again communication means it
再次写入 通信意味着它首先
increases the reach of communication
增加了通信的范围
first of all you reach people who aren't
there when you were communicating
当您以其他方式进行交流时不在场的人，
otherwise and that helps if people
如果人们
aren't in the same room or at the same
不在同一个房间或同一
time zone etc etc also for non-native
时区等，这对非
speakers it really makes it easier to
母语人士也有帮助
slowly sometimes read what's been said
and try to understand an ongoing
并尝试理解正在进行的
conversation such written communication
对话，这样的书面交流
creates transparency transparency
创造了透明度透明度
combined with archiving traceability and
与存档可追溯性和历史记录相结合，
history that really makes communication
这确实使交流
easier and creates also - helps create
更容易，也创造了 - 有助于建立
that trust that makes people want to
让人们想要
join because the project is honest and
加入的信任，因为项目是诚实和
open writing emails is actually
开放的，写电子邮件实际上是
surprisingly hard we will look at that a
令人惊讶的 很难，我们稍后会
little bit later again here's some very
再看一下这里有一些非常
basic practices like email should have
基本的做法，比如电子邮件应该有
one purpose and if you have multiple
一个目的，如果你有多个
things put them into different emails so
东西把它们放在不同的电子邮件中，
that the subject line actually is
这样主题行实际上是
descriptive of the email then there are
对电子邮件的描述，那么就
debatable practices top quoting what
有争议的做法顶部 引用什么
encoding etc things like that to
编码之类的东西来
consider fine third our communication
考虑第三个我们的交流
open communication and projects
开放交流 ion and projects
open-source projects should be complete
开源项目应该是完整的，
so if it's complete again everyone can
所以如果它再次完成，每个人都可以
participate and also it really helps
参与，而且它真的可以帮助
people who are new to the project to
刚接触该项目的人
more easily get up to speed and again
更容易上手，
this way it creates more trust and
这样它会创造更多的信任和
credibility and finally open-source
可信度并最终开放 -源
communication or open communications
通信或开放式通信
craft that has some practical benefits
技术具有一些实际好处，
like an immediate documentation of what
例如立即记录
has been going on but also it actually
正在发生的事情，但
disciplines communication if you know
如果您
what you're saying or writing to a
知道自己在说什么或写信到
mailing list will be archived forever
邮件列表，它实际上会规范沟通，
you will be rather low-key on offending
您将永远存档 冒犯
people and you will be focused on the
别人时低调，你将专注于
content of the arguments rather than
争论的内容而不是
offending other people so that also that
冒犯其他人，这样
increased discipline creates more trust
增加的纪律也为项目创造了更多的信任
and credibility for the projects this
和可信度，
way actually open source projects found
实际上开源项目找到
a way to to document themselves
了一种方法来记录
everyone knows how hard and how poor the
每个人 知道
documentation of almost all software
几乎所有软件
projects is open-source a lot and by
项目的文档都是开源的有多难和多差，并且
requiring written and archived public
需要 g
within our public complete with an
在我们的公众中书面和存档的公众完成
archived document communication open
存档文档通信
source projects literally document
开源项目从字面上记录
themselves because all important
自己，因为所有重要的
decisions need to go through the mailing
决定通常都需要通过邮件
list typically and will be archived and
列表并且将被存档，并且
the discipline of such communication
此类通信的纪律
means that at the end of some discussion
意味着在一些讨论结束时
when a decision is being made there will
当做出决定时，将会
be a summary email of the person asking
有一封询问并最终做出最终摘要的人的摘要电子邮件，
and making ultimately the final summary
最终摘要
has to make a summary of that decision
必须对该决定进行摘要
and it will go to the mailing next arc
，并将发送到邮件下一个弧形
mailing is archived and thereby there is
邮件被存档，因此
now a documented thread with a
现在有一个记录的线程 关于
conclusion as to why a particular
为什么做出特定
decision was cast this is a good way of
决定的结论，这是一种自我记录的好方法，
self documenting which actually happens
它实际上发生
in the act and thereby is helpful to the
在行为中，从而有助于
engineers to the developers as they go
工程师对开发人员
about the daily business which is so
进行日常业务，这
much better than trying to document
比尝试
things after the fact and you actually
事后记录事情，你实际上
have no incentive or motivation to do
没有动机或动机去做
that documentation so open source
那些文件，所以公开酸 ce
projects in some sense
项目在某种意义上
correct a key aspect of a good
纠正了一个好的文档的一个关键方面，
documentation that usually is something
这通常
that developers don't like to do and
是开发人员不喜欢做的事情，
again communication is so important
而且沟通是如此重要，
there are lots and lots of practices to
这里有很多很多的实践可以
follow here I think from the Fogle book
遵循我认为来自 Fogle 书
and some others and we will look at some
和其他一些 在合作之后，我们现在也会看看其中
of those nature as well now after
的一些性质
collaboration the three principles of
open collaboration and the four
开放式协作的三个原则和
practices of open communication the five
开放式沟通的四个实践
stages of volunteering here is bill and
这里志愿服务的五个阶段
offs model of project integration and he
是项目整合的账单和关闭模式，他
sees the argues that it's this increment
认为这是这种增量
incremental step wise engagement of
users and developers with a project
用户和开发人员逐步逐步参与项目
where they have some initial need or
，他们有一些初始需求或
actual problem they're trying to fix and
他们试图解决的实际问题，
then they escalate and stages and
然后他们升级和分阶段，
potentially in the end they become a
最终他们可能成为
leader of the project so as part of
项目的领导者，作为
solving their own problem engaged with
解决他们的一部分 自己的问题
the project build rapport all in love
与项目建立融洽关系是否热爱
with the project or not the Syndicates
项目辛迪加
not contributing all the way to
没有为
potentially leading the project now I
潜在的贡献 y 现在领导该项目，我
will recast that as the five star
将把它改写为五星级
overcast that s the five stages of
阴天，这是
applesauce volunteering to make it much
苹果酱自愿使其更
simpler and we will describe these I
简单的五个阶段，我们将描述这些我
will describe these five stages using
将使用
the best practices that are being
applied as part of these five five
作为其中一部分应用的最佳实践来描述这五个阶段 五个五个
stages where best practice is basically
阶段，最佳实践基本上
a broadly accepted often informally
是一种被广泛接受的通常非正式
defined method for achieving something
定义的方法，用于实现某
doing something and yeah so we should
事做某事，是的，所以我们应该
have seen here our here we go
在这里看到我们的这里我们开始
our five stages of open source
我们的开源
volunteering and here you can see those
志愿服务的五个阶段，在这里你可以看到这
five stages what's noteworthy is that it
五个阶段值得注意的是 它
takes a dual or comp
需要志愿者的双重或组合
entry view of the volunteer has a broad
条目视图在
broad brush stroke role here and the
这里具有广泛的笔触角色和
project view and we can see how a
项目视图，我们可以看到
volunteer goes through the five stages
志愿者如何经历
of finding a project for that problem
为该问题找到项目的五个阶段
understanding the project engaging with
了解项目
the project working with the project and
与项目的互动 与项目一起工作，
finally becoming a leader of the project
最终成为项目
themselves and the project view where
本身和
the project needs or wants to find
项目需要或想要的项目视图的领导者 找到
volunteers and work with them so the
志愿者并与他们一起工作，因此志愿者
project view for each of the stages of
每个阶段的项目视图
the volunteer needs to be available to
需要首先通过营销项目向他们提供，
them first by marketing the project
explaining the project engaging with a
解释项目与
volunteer working with a contributor and
志愿者与贡献者一起工作，
then enabling a career as a project
然后成为项目
leader so these five stages we will look
负责人 我们将详细介绍这五个阶段
at in detail so here is stage stage one
，所以
for the volunteer from the volunteers
从志愿者的
perspective they want to find a project
角度来看，这是志愿者的第一阶段，他们想要找到一个项目，
so they have that edge they have that
所以他们有优势，他们有这个
problem and they want to find a matching
问题，他们想要找到一个匹配的
project and the two best practices if
项目和两个最佳实践 如果
you will are that they simply by lucky
您会认为他们只是
chance stumble on the project also
偶然偶然发现了该项目，那
that's just lucky chance or maybe they
也只是幸运的机会，或者他们
hear about it all because they
听说这一切是因为他们
deliberately want to fix or solve the
故意想修复或解决
problem they actively search for it
问题，他们会
using some such engine so this is simply
使用某些此类引擎积极搜索它，所以这只是
things that volunteers do not
事情 志愿者
necessarily with the goal in mind of
不一定以
joining the project just with the goal
加入项目为目标
of fixing their particular problem now
，只是为了解决他们现在的特定问题
for this to work the project are and the
，以使其发挥作用 项目是，其
project leaders behind it or the current
背后的项目负责人或
team of the software of the open-source
开源项目的当前软件团队
project needs to make that possible so
需要使这成为可能，因此
it needs to enable stumbling upon the
它需要能够偶然发现
project it needs to make the project
项目，它需要
findable through general or
通过通用或
domain-specific search engines so the
特定领域的搜索引擎找到该项目 所以这个
project for that needs to be prepared
项目需要准备，
we found it needs to perform active
我们发现它需要进行积极的
outreach which has basic best practices
外展，这有基本的最佳实践，
like having a good name understanding
比如有一个好的名字，
the channels or the ways of how
了解渠道或志愿者喜欢项目的方式，以及
volunteers like the project and being
active on those channels etc so here are
在这些渠道上的活跃等等，所以这里有
a couple of channels of how projects may
一个 项目如何
market themselves there are is the basic
推销自己的几个渠道
website for the project that can get
项目的基本网站可以
picked up by search engines so search
被搜索引擎收录，因此搜索
engine optimization plays a role then
引擎优化发挥作用，然后
projects can put up large projects
项目可以提出大型项目
important projects can show up at
重要项目可以出现
conferences where they prevent
在他们阻止的会议上
themselves or in the case of foundations
他们自己，或者在基金会的情况下，
even have their own conferences such
甚至有自己的会议，这样的
projects may announce anything they have
项目可能会宣布他们必须说的任何事情，
to say not only on their own channels
不仅 在他们自己的渠道（
like our mailing list but going through
例如我们的邮件列表）上，但通过已
established channels like I can use or
建立的渠道（例如我可以使用或
reddit also priming those and/or using
reddit 也启动这些渠道和/或使用
Twitter etc so this is literally
Twitter 等），所以这实际上
marketing marketing channels as we know
是我们所知道的营销渠道
it and open source projects have to do
，开源项目必须这样
that - so you're a banette need a
做 - 所以你 '是一个班内特需要一个
project needs to be active about
项目需要积极
marketing it and it also needs to deal
营销它，它还需要
with the potential inflow now of of
处理感兴趣的各方现在的潜在流入
interested parties and that's a passive
，这是一种被动
inflow where again they need to register
流入，他们需要再次注册
themselves so that they can be found
自己，以便可以找到他们
register themselves on all relevant
注册自己 所有相关的
places so such relevant places are
地方，所以这些相关的地方
basically poets like
基本上是像
ollo or open half the former ollo and
ollo 这样的诗人或打开前 ollo 的一半
some of us many of these portals these
，我们中的一些人这些
days are actually defunct so they were
天实际上已经
not particularly strong didn't have a
不存在了，所以它们不是特别强大没有
good business model but say github would
良好的商业模式，但说 github 会
for
well even if you're not actually doing
好吧，即使您实际上并没有在
github development on github
github 上进行 github 开发，
so we will look at tooling later on how
所以我们稍后将研究工具，了解
open-source innovation also applied to
开源创新如何也应用于
software tooling and we just say here
软件工具，我们 只是在这里
that software forges our tool invention
说软件通过开源社区的开源伪造了我们的工具发明
by open source by the open source
，
community at large and that these forges
并且这些伪造
support this particular process of a
支持
marketer marketing outreach and be
营销人员营销推广的特定过程，并
accepting or being prepared for passive
接受或准备被动
inflow and we'll see that later so then
流入，我们稍后会看到
in a second step the volunteer who
在第二步中，志愿者
somehow now found a project they are
现在不知何故找到了一个他们
interested in our cut out of curiosity
对我们感兴趣的项目，
or because it's also fixes a particular
或者因为它也为他们解决了一个特定
problem for them the volunteer finds a
问题，志愿者发现
project lab in itself does not mean much
项目实验室本身并没有多大意义，
because now the volunteer is staring at
因为现在志愿者正在盯着
some website and needs to understand the
一些网站，需要了解该
project so they want to read up on it
项目，因此他们想阅读它
that's the goal for that to work the
这是该项目工作的目标，该
project needs to explain itself how to
项目需要解释自己如何
do that right is again a set of best
做到这一点再次是一组最佳
practices for example to have a clear
实践，例如有一个明确的
mission statement that explains what the
使命宣言 解释
project is about it needs to provide
项目是关于它需要提供
examples and screenshots to create some
示例和屏幕截图以创建一些
intuition state the license and the
直觉状态许可证和
terms of the project make it simple to
项目的条款使其变得简单
download things etc etc simply making it
下载东西等等 只是
easy really easy to the potential
让潜在的志愿者很容易
volunteer the visitor perhaps only at
访问者可能只有在
this stage to learn what the project is
这个阶段才能了解项目的
all about so that the visitor can
全部内容，以便访问者有
potentially become a volunteer well
可能成为一名志愿者，
first of all just perhaps a user and
首先可能只是一个用户，
then a volunteer for volunteering of
然后是一名志愿者 对于志愿服务，
course
the project needs to state its rules of
项目当然需要说明其参与规则，
engagement which is part of explaining
这是
how that particular project community
解释特定项目社区如何
works here you can see a project
运作的一部分在这里你可以看到一个项目
homepage where you can see the name the
主页，在那里你可以看到名称
license some social aspects of heard how
许可证的一些社会方面听说
it's been ranked and rated all
它是如何排名和评级的 所有
screenshots making it really easy to
屏幕截图使下载软件变得非常容易
download the software etc alright so the
等等好吧，所以
volunteer now wants to engage with the
志愿者现在想要参与该
project so they found a project and they
项目，所以他们找到了一个项目并
read up on it and so they like what they
阅读了它，所以他们喜欢他们
see and use want to use the project if
看到和使用的东西，如果
the project was set up properly then
该项目想要使用该项目 设置正确，然后
using the software shouldn't be too hard
使用该软件应该不会太难，
but maybe they're things that are not
但也许它们是不
easily done or not that they'll explain
容易完成的事情，或者他们不会解释，
so it might be that the volunteer has to
所以它可能 是志愿者必须
ask a question about how to use the
问一个关于如何使用该
software for that the volunteer can of
软件的问题，因为志愿者
course just ask that question but a good
当然可以只问这个问题，但是一个好的
volunteer will actually do the homework
志愿者实际上会先做功课
first
and communicate well how what what the
并很好地交流什么
will communicate well what the problem
会很好地交流什么问题
is and we look at that in a second so
是什么 我们很快就会看到这
for that the reason why a volunteer
一点，因此志愿者
cannot just barge in demand attention
不能只是强行要求关注
and be satisfied is why would they why
并感到满意的原因是，他们为什么
would the project help the potential
要该项目帮助
volunteer they have no incentive unless
他们没有动力的潜在志愿者，除非
they really believe that person will be
他们真的相信那个人会有所
helpful to the project at all the
帮助 对于项目一
beginning that we adjust the distraction
开始，我们会调整分心
and in fact as we will see in a bit
，事实上，正如我们将看到的那样，
most people who ask questions will just
大多数提出问题的人只会
consume time and effort and there won't
消耗时间和精力，并且不会
be any payback for the part
有任何回报，
so a volunteer or smart person who wants
所以志愿者或聪明人
to ask questions about the project does
谁想询问有关该
so in a way that it indicates they're
项目的问题，这表明他们是
honest and open and put in some legwork
诚实和开放的，并且自己进行了一些跑腿工作
themselves and are not just stealing the
，而不仅仅是在窃取
existing developers time so for that the
现有的开发人员 现在是时候了，
volunteer obviously need to browser on
志愿者显然需要
the website typically understand a
浏览网站，通常了解
little bit about the practices for
一些关于战争的做法
example war and how to ask a question
以及如何提出问题，
and be willing to accept any guidance as
并愿意在
they ask a question for example so
他们提出问题时接受任何指导，所以
here's a typical way of doing that I
这是一种典型的方式 我
just picked it from a random open source
只是从一个随机的开源
project someone is asking a question I
项目中挑选它有人在问一个问题我
have a problem is using the software
有一个问题是使用该软件
it's the typical request for help as you
这是典型的帮助请求，因为你
can see that person asks troubles a
可以看到那个人
little bit while not brothers but points
虽然不是兄弟但会提出一些麻烦但
out okay I'm here for the first time
指出好的 我是第一次来这里，
please forgive me if I'm making a
如果我犯了错误，请原谅我，
mistake
but then actually follows a reasonable
但实际上是遵循合理的
email it's first of our description so
电子邮件，这是我们的第一个描述，
it's clear they have a problem it's
所以很明显他们有问题
clear from the subject line then they
从主题行中很明显，然后他们
say ok I'm here for the first time then
说好的，我是 第一次在这里，然后
they describe the situation and then
他们描述情况，然后
they describe the problem with the
他们
situation in a descriptive positive way
以描述性积极的方式描述情况的问题，
they simply say what the setup is and
他们简单地说设置是什么，
then what they do and the outcome they
然后他们做了什么以及结果t 嘿，
get from it and why it's not the
从中得到，为什么这不是
expected outcome there's no complaining
预期的结果，这里没有抱怨
here for example how crappy the software
，例如软件有多糟糕
is that it leads to a problem obviously
，它会导致问题
that would be would lead the questioner
显然会导致
the person asking the question to
提问者提出问题的
remediate to being ignored immediately
人立即被忽略，
so this is a reasonable email asking for
所以这是 一封合理的寻求
help and asking questions has really
帮助和提问的电子邮件确实
taught that easy well it is easy once
教会了你很容易，一旦
you know how to do it but if you've
你知道怎么做就很容易，但是如果你
swaggered with a problem for too long
对一个问题大摇大摆太久，
you're easily tempted to not write a
你很容易不想写一个
good question
好问题
so at that time you need to take a step
所以在 那个时候你需要退后一步
back and ask maybe crew down and then
，问一下船员，然后
ask the question properly so here's a
正确地问这个问题，所以这里有一个
simple way how to ask a question
简单的方法来问
suggested to by my one reader of our
我的一位读者建议的
work and he said like you should first
问题，他说你应该先
say what you want I would like to do X
说你想要什么 我想做X
then what you tried to achieve that that
然后你试图实现的那
already might be an indicator to a
可能已经向
reader that you're that you're trying
读者表明你正在
the wrong thing perhaps and then what
尝试错误的事情，然后
happened and perhaps why it's not the
发生了什么，也许为什么它不是你的
thing you expected to happen in addition
事情 你预计还会发生，
since usually this is some sort of
因为通常这是
debugging going on through a mailing
通过邮件
list make sure that you include all
列表进行的某种调试确保您包含所有
relevant information or operating system
相关信息或
you're running in the oceans etc etc
您在海洋中运行的操作系统等等等，
this guy also says no attachments that's
这家伙还说没有附件
not a good thing for the typical open
不好 典型的
source mailing lists and really really
开源邮件列表的东西，真的
make it short long emails usually don't
让它很短很长的电子邮件通常不会
get read TLDR as you probably know
被阅读 TLDR，因为你可能知道
here's another article from the web by
这是 Raymond 和 Lauren 的另一篇来自网络的文章，
Raymond and Lauren on how to ask
关于如何以
questions the smart way this collection
聪明的方式提问这个集合
is of advice is interesting in that it's
是建议 有趣的是它
rather rude as the open source
相当粗鲁，因为开源
communities sometimes in the
社区有时在
communication at all can be quite rude
交流中可能非常粗鲁
and you can see how it's very
，你可以看到它是如何非常
detail-oriented but practical practical
注重细节但实用的实用
advice I'm not going into every little
建议我不会深入到
aspect of this year you can read it up
今年的每一个小方面你可以 阅读它
just go to the literature section of the
只需转到课程的文献部分
course look up RM 14 and read up on some
查找 RM 14 并阅读其中的
of this advice if you like to so
一些建议，如果你愿意的话
communication of mailing lists is so
，邮件列表的沟通是如此
important that that some foundations of
重要 一些
projects have literally set up etiquette
项目的基础实际上已经在礼仪上设置了礼仪
on etiquette for how to act properly
，从如何正确行事一直
all the way down to how to format
到如何格式化主题
subjects how to format the emails all
如何格式化电子邮件一直
the way to styles of writing we
到写作风格我们众所
well-known netiquette um this doesn't
周知的网络礼仪嗯这实际
actually begin and end with open source
上并不 以开源项目开始和结束
projects really all open collaboration
真的所有的开放协作
projects are like that
项目都是这样的
here's advice from the former director
这里是来自
executive director of the Wikimedia
维基媒体基金会前执行董事的建议
Foundation sue Gardner on on how to
sue Gardner 关于如何
communicate with a community of within
与社区内的
community and this advice is actually
社区进行交流，这个建议实际上是
very good advice and you can read up
非常好的建议，你 也可以
under the reference g16 about it are too
在参考 g16 下阅读有关它的信息
so then back to stage 3 where we are
，然后回到第 3 阶段，我们正在
engaging with a volunteer this is the
与志愿者互动，这是
project perspective so there is now that
项目视角，所以现在有
visitor who or potential volunteer and
访客或潜在志愿者，
they asked the question perhaps so how
他们可能问了这个问题，所以
do you engage with that person first of
你如何参与 首先，
all you need to make it possible that
你需要让
the person asks that question so you
那个人问那个问题成为可能，这样你就
make clear or explicit how they can ask
可以清楚或明确地说明他们如何问
questions how you can be reached what is
问题 关于如何联系到您 什么
the appropriate mailing list or the
是适当的邮件列表或
appropriate forum since the goal is to
适当的论坛，因为目标是
acquire people as volunteers you need to
招募志愿者作为志愿者，您需要
make them feel at home so you might want
让他们有宾至如归的感觉，所以
to welcome them if they register for a
如果他们注册一个项目，您可能想要欢迎他们
project maybe they have a person
也许他们有一个 个人
specific website leave a small note
特定网站在那里留下一个小便条
there like the Wikipedia community does
，就像维基百科社区确实
leave a small note there welcoming that
在那里留下一个小便条欢迎那
person to the community in general don't
个人加入社区一般
be rude which is a particular challenge
不要粗鲁，这是一个特别的挑战
open source projects which are based on
开源项目基于
which are not necessarily strong on
它不一定在
social graces just look at the iron 14
社交方面很强大 优雅只看前面的 Iron 14
example from earlier and the general
示例
aspects of open communication apply
，开放式沟通的一般方面适用，
avoid private
避免私人
Cashion's etc etc still you will have to
Cashion 等，你仍然必须
accept some redundancy so if someone
接受一些冗余，所以如果有人
asks the same question that others have
问其他人问过的相同问题，
asked don't be rude
不要
like RTFM them or tell them to simply
像 RTFM 那样粗鲁他们 或者告诉他们简单的
plain D and frankly I'll point them to
D 坦率地说，我会把他们
the mailing list archives where maybe
指向邮件列表档案，在那里可能
the question has been answered before
已经回答了这个问题，
since you're also thinking about
因为你也是 考虑
potentially acquiring volunteers and
潜在的招募志愿者，
only might you answer their questions
只有你能回答他们的问题，
you should also make very visible simple
你还应该做一些非常明显的简单
basic tasks that someone could pick up
基本任务，有人可以接受
who is grateful for having received good
那些对收到好的答案表示感谢的人，
answers for example to the problem to
例如为项目做出贡献的问题，
make a contribution to the project so
所以
basic practices on on on how to glue
基本的实践 关于如何将人员粘合
people on board so since they're
在一起，因此由于他们是
different volunteers potential
不同的志愿者，
volunteers or contributors there might
因此可能是潜在的志愿者或贡献者，可能
be the non-technical person who could
会有非技术人员可以
help with marketing and bug reports
帮助进行营销和错误报告
there also of course there are the
，当然还有
technical people developers so for those
技术人员开发人员，因此对于那些
technical people you need extra best
技术人员 您需要额外的最佳
practices you need to provide tool
实践 您需要为他们提供工具
access for them to them you may give
访问权限 您可以授予
them some access rights to the bug
他们对错误跟踪器的一些访问权限，
trackers so to file a bug if you didn't
以便提交错误，如果您没有
make it public from the get-go you show
从一开始就将其公开 您向
them the project roadmap and the
他们展示项目路线图 以及
requirements etc etc and suddenly you
需求等，突然你
need to provide some documentation even
需要提供一些文档，
if it's just a wiki with the links in to
即使它只是一个包含
all the main decisions are as as derived
所有主要决策链接的 wiki 就像
in communication on a mailing list okay
邮件列表上的交流一样，
so the project is preparing itself to
所以该项目正在准备自己
potentially acquire volunteers but that
可能获得志愿者，但这
is hard there's quite a gap from between
很难，从
asking a question and becoming someone
提出问题到成为
who spends their time on helping a
花时间帮助
project
项目的人之间存在相当大的差距
so in order to motivate people one needs
，以便激励 人们
to understand their motivations there's
需要了解他们的动机
a fair bit of research out there why
有大量的研究 为什么
people are participate on open-source
人们会参与开源
projects is a collection of key
项目 关键动机的集合
motivations there's the original
有问题的原始
technical motivation the person has a
技术动机
problem is looking for a solution in the
正在寻找
form of software typically there is
软件形式的解决方案 通常有
economic motivation at least
经济动机 至少
hypothesized economic motivation develop
假设的经济动机 产生
a signal there are capabilities to the
一个信号
labor market for future employment
劳动力市场有能力为未来的就业提供
perhaps so they simply show how capable
可能，所以他们只是展示了
they are and as we will also see later a
他们的能力，正如我们稍后会看到的
subset of developers smart developers
一部分开发人员聪明的开发人员
see open-source work as a career path
看到开源工作 作为
for a stronger economic negotiation
position with employees as well the
与员工和
social motivation might go beyond the
社会加强经济谈判地位的职业道路 l 动机可能超越
technical motivation be the most
技术动机，
important one people like working in
communities if they feel valued if they
如果他们觉得自己的贡献会有所作为，那么他们会觉得在社区中工作是最重要的动机，
think their contributions make a
difference so some people feel validated
所以
if you're good about being in a
如果你擅长在
community simply enjoy the work with
社区中工作，那么一些人会觉得得到了认可
other people they like and that is what
他们喜欢的其他人，这就是
you need to utilize or what a project
你需要利用的东西，或者项目
needs to utilize to get to that first
需要利用的东西来获得第一个
contribution that's the first major
贡献，这是第一个主要的
horror how do you get how do you get
恐怖你如何得到你如何让
someone to spend their personal time
某人通常花费他们的个人时间
typically to contribute to a project so
来为项目做出贡献
the most basic thing to get right is to
所以最基本的事情是
make it easy to have a make a first
让第一次
contribution make the bug tracker open
贡献变得容易 让错误跟踪器打开
so if someone wants to file a bug then
所以如果有人想提交错误，那么
they wouldn't they shouldn't have to ask
他们就不会，他们不应该让不认识
an unknown person to get access to the
的人得到 访问
backtrack I simply allow people to
回溯我只是让人们在
firebox period make it open available
火箱期间让它
for everyone then as you perhaps lay out
对所有人开放然后你可能
in a document of the roadmap of the
在项目路线图的文件中列出
project there should be super town
应该有超级
as mentioned already but also make these
城镇 已经提到过，但也使这些
contributions and simple tasks
贡献和简单任务
incremental in that they build on each
递增，因为它们相互建立
other and people can go from smaller to
，人们可以从较小的贡献变成
larger contributions so this way anyone
更大的贡献，所以这样
who has time to spare who thinks this
任何有时间空闲的人认为这个
project might be good for them and wants
项目可能对他们有好处并
to contribute finds that easy to
想要贡献发现
contribute in addition to bringing those
除了让那些自己管理项目负责人的人参与进来之外，这很容易做出贡献，
on board who by themselves steward a
project leader the project might also
该项目还可能会
call out laureates from the shadows so
从阴影中召集获奖者，这样
you can actively on the mailing list ask
您就可以积极地在邮件列表中
for help by pointing out that simple
通过指出需要完成简单的任务来寻求帮助，
tasks need to be done and whether there
并且 是否
wouldn't be anyone who's been benefiting
不会有人
from the project and likes the project
从该项目中受益并喜欢该项目
and that's maybe why they on the mailing
，这可能就是为什么他们在邮件
list but hasn't done anything yet so you
列表中但还没有做任何事情所以你
call them out from the shadows the so
把他们从阴影中
called lockers to call them out and
叫出来所谓的储物柜叫他们出来
maybe that's how they get to make the
也许这就是他们做出
first contribution so again for just
第一个贡献的方式，所以再次
make it really easy to support that
让支持变得非常容易，
it's how the tooling of open-source
这就是开源
software development supports the
软件开发人员的工具 t 支持
processes in particular the engineering
流程，特别是流程的工程
aspects of the processes to make that
方面，以使
open collaboration happen easily and
开放式协作轻松
smoothly the volunteer let's assume
顺利地进行 志愿者让我们假设
they've made the first contribution and
他们已经做出了第一个贡献
the second or third contribution and
和第二个或第三个贡献，
maybe they are so-called peripheral or
也许他们是所谓的外围或
episodic volunteer or maybe they are a
偶发志愿者或 也许他们现在是一名
regular volunteer now I just have fun
普通的志愿者我只是玩得开心
maybe it's some spare time maybe it's
也许这是一些业余时间也许
actually paid time to be a good
实际上是有偿成为一名优秀的
volunteer you need to be responsive and
志愿者您需要在做出贡献时反应迅速且
reliable as you contribute as we
可靠，因为我们
contribute that's of course the
做出了贡献这当然是
essential aspect if you don't you fall
必不可少的方面 如果您
by the wayside and reliability again
再次陷入困境和可靠性，
then perhaps the ignored the project or
那么也许被忽视的项目
the project leaders really need to keep
或项目负责人真的需要继续
knighting that that fire or keep people
为那场火灾或让人们
motivated to contribute and again it
有动力做出贡献，这再次
means that the software or the project
意味着软件或项目
has to be structured in a way that it's
的结构必须以一种方式 很
easy to keep people involved and
容易让人们参与并
involved in their various best practices
参与他们的各种最佳实践，
to follow one perhaps debatable question
以遵循一个可能有争议的问题
is that the project should have a
是 p  roject 应该有一个
component oriented set up so that there
面向组件的设置，以便
is ownership and that it's clear who to
有所有权，并且很清楚要
ask that everyone will agree because
问谁，每个人都会同意，因为
they add a development which is more
他们添加了一个更面向未来的开发，
future oriented will say well everyone
会说每个人都
can change and everything and we take a
可以改变和一切，我们采用
feature of functional antic perspective
功能性的特性
so open-source will have to combine that
因此，开源项目必须将其结合起来，
by historically open source projects
从历史上看，开源项目
have always been component oriented
一直是面向组件的，
mostly because my relief originally most
主要是因为我松了一口气，最初大多数
open source projects have been
开源项目都已
distributed to nature and if you are
分发给大自然，如果您
distributed working in a distributed
以分布式方式进行分布式工作，
fashion you simply divvy up work in such
您只需将工作分配给 这样
a way that people have clear
一种方式，人们有明确的
responsibilities and that's usually most
责任，通常最
easily done by aligning people's
容易通过将人们的
responsibilities with technical
责任与
component of boundaries nevertheless in
边界的技术部分保持一致来完成。然而，
order to get work done and keep
为了完成工作并保持
motivated work keep keep people
积极的工作，保持人们的
motivated you should give them features
积极性，你应该给他们特性，
even if those features mean that the
即使这些特性意味着
developer has to touch multiple
开发人员必须
components as if that person the
像那个人一样触摸多个组件
developer here is still a volunteer was
这里的开发人员仍然是一名志愿者，他们
contributing what actually can't change
贡献了实际上无法
the codebase they may have to touch
更改代码库的内容，他们可能不得不接触
different components and submit to the
不同的组件，并向
different component owners the
不同的组件所有者
committees for those components their
提交这些组件的委员会，他们
particular suggested changes that can be
提出的特定更改可能
quite tricky because you need to
非常棘手，因为您需要
coordinate all these changes ideally
协调 理想情况下，所有这些更改都很
it's simple and one person can enact all
简单，一个人可以制定所有
those changes even if they if it
这些更改，即使它们
requires review by different people so
需要由不同的人进行审查，所以
here's a little bit of a distinction
这里有一点
the project wants to work with the new
区别，项目希望与新
contributors or someone making their
贡献者或做出
first contribution where is this little
第一次贡献的人一起工作这是哪里 一个小
blip that this person who's making
问题，这个做出
contribution might be someone to be
贡献的人可能会在
there longer time no you don't know so
那里待更长时间，不，你不知道，所以
you don't want to make life hard for
你不想让他们的生活变得艰难，
them as they are the link to spend some
因为他们是花一些时间的纽带，
time so very basic react speedily thank
所以非常基本的快速反应谢谢
them and we Expedia to whatever
他们 我们 Expedia
contribution they are making certainly
对他们所做的任何贡献当然
don't sit on say patches that they've
不会坐以待毙，说
been provided that doesn't mean you need
他们提供的补丁并不意味着你
to be thankful and the sense of simply
accepting anything that comes along by
the opposite as the project as a project
作为项目
leader or committer you have a
负责人或提交者，您有
responsibility to maintain the quality
责任保持质量，
and effectively you actually need to
并且您实际上需要
guide any new contributor so to make any
指导任何新的贡献者，以便在项目中做出任何
contributions in the best possible way
贡献。 最好的
that actually means you have to guide
方法实际上意味着您必须指导
them for example to accept basic
他们，例如接受
programming guidelines that the project
项目同意的基本编程指南，
has agreed to if they ignore those well
如果他们忽略了那些
a good volunteer would have read up on
好的志愿者会阅读
the project it will have chosen the
该项目，它将选择
proper programming guidelines but if
正确的编程指南，但如果
they didn't then it's got to be a back
他们没有那么它必须
and forth and guidance by the project
是项目负责人的来回和指导，以
leaders that guides the new contributor
指导新
to understand the ways of the project
贡献者了解项目的方式
and address to that for that reason
并解决这个问题，因此
basically contributions need to be
基本上贡献需要在
charted conversations between the
contributor and the receiving committee
贡献者和
who engages with the contributor to make
与贡献者合作以
sure things fit small patches usually
确保内容适合小补丁的接收委员会
get in pretty easily large patches are a
通常很容易进入 大补丁是个
bad idea so there are lots of best
坏主意，所以有很多
practices of how a smart contributor
关于聪明的贡献者
works with the project for example by
如何与项目合作的最佳实践，例如
first discussing what they want to do on
首先讨论他们想在邮件列表上做什么，
the mailing list basically then raising
然后
the hand that they're telling the world
举手告诉
that they're going to do this and then
全世界他们 '要这样做，然后
incrementally working on it
逐步进行工作，
and gathering feedback from the rest of
并从团队其他成员那里收集反馈，
the team that's how you get larger
这就是你如何
changes into a project because you don't
在项目中进行更大的更改，因为你不会
suddenly surprise everyone with one
突然用一个大补丁让每个人都感到惊讶，
large patch that it's just too large to
因为它太大而不能
leave you and again project leaders who
离开你 再次考虑项目
have the longevity and quality of the
的寿命和质量的
project in mind are more likely to
项目负责人更有可能
reject any large patch and a large
拒绝任何
contribution that I can't quality assess
我无法质量评估的大补丁和大贡献，
and rather than accept it
而不是接受它，
so contributions need to be high quality
因此贡献需要高质量，
otherwise they simply get rejected
否则他们只会得到
anyway so again going back to the
无论如何都被拒绝了，所以再次回到
project as it is working with a new
项目，因为它正在与新的
contributor the project the key
贡献者合作项目关键
developers core committers
开发人员核心提交者
etc they need to react speedily they
等他们需要快速反应他们
need to create communication and
需要 创建交流和
contribution will enter conversation and
贡献将进入对话，
I need to provide code review and
我需要提供代码审查和
feedback until the contributions right
反馈，直到贡献正确
usually it's not right right file right
通常它不正确
from the get-go they need to provide
从一开始就提交文件，他们需要提供
credit so the developer the new
信用，因此新
contributor now commits are now a
贡献者现在提交的开发人员现在是
contributor and the former user now in
贡献者 前用户现在在
new countries then a new contributor
新的国家 然后是新的贡献者
one-step submission the tasks are
一步提交 任务被
accepted
接受
they want to see credit that makes them
他们希望看到让他们
feel good that creates that potential
感觉良好的功劳 创造
enjoyment of participating in the
参与
project and etc so this is a way of how
项目的潜在乐趣等等 所以这是一种
you bring you new contributors on board
方式 现在为您带来新的贡献者
now a new contributor will challenge
新的贡献者将
regular contributor over time about
随着时间的推移挑战常规贡献者 关于
Samba not bats are Sundra and those who
Samba 不是蝙蝠是 Sundra 以及那些
become regular contributors as a project
成为常规贡献者作为项目
leader you have to track their interests
负责人的人 您必须跟踪他们的兴趣
you can pull them out you can assign to
您可以将他们拉出来 您可以分配给
them perhaps some tasks etc there's a
他们 也许一些 任务等这里发生了
subtle shift going on here a new
微妙的转变，一个新的
contributor probably is making
贡献者可能正在
contribution with respect to the thing
对这件事做出贡献
that was their problem to begin with so
帽子是他们一开始的问题，所以
maybe the project solved their problem
也许项目解决了他们的问题，
but only 80 percent so they programmed
但只有 80%，所以他们自己编程
the missing 20% themselves the initial
了缺失的 20%
connection with a project is always
almost always specific to the problem at
hand
why any later engagement if there is
loyalty with the project may well go
这个项目很可能会
beyond the specific problem they
超越他们
initially had to a broader support of
最初遇到的具体问题，而是更广泛地
the project that is also not only how
支持项目，这不仅
the project leaders come about who we
是项目负责人如何产生我们
talk about but simply how long-term
谈论的人，而且仅仅是长期
volunteers are come about who do things
志愿者如何产生谁做的
that are not necessarily fun and that
事情 不一定很有趣，
don't necessarily fix their actual
也不一定能解决他们手头的实际
problem at hand but are simply good and
问题，但对于项目来说只是好和
important for the project like cleaning
重要，比如
up a wiki or sometimes going to a
清理 wiki 或有时去参加
conference and marketing being a booth
会议和营销作为展位
or marketing the project things like
或营销项目
that that don't actually have much to do
这样的事情 实际上
anything any longer was their original
，他们不再有太多事情
motivation to join the project anyway so
you work with a regular contributor you
track the interests and you try to meet
要做了 ests 并且您尝试满足
the interests so that they have fun
他们的兴趣，以便他们有乐趣
contributing you also slowly start
做出贡献您也慢慢开始
sharing with them not only technical
与他们分享不仅是技术
work but that's managerial work and as
工作，而且是管理工作，当
you work with them you demonstrate that
您与他们一起工作时，您证明了
as a project either you demonstrate that
作为一个项目，您要么证明
you're serious about it which means you
您是认真的 这意味着
follow up if they accepted a task but
如果他们接受了一项任务但
nothing is happening
什么都没有发生，
you follow up and you ask why nothing is
你会跟进你跟进，你问为什么什么都没有
happening and if it all fails that means
发生，如果一切都失败了，这意味着
you will have to a little bit
你将不得不有点
embarrassed and then pull out so that's
尴尬然后退出，
that's how it is so you now have regular
这就是它的样子 所以你现在有固定的
contributors and they should be
贡献者，他们应该
participating in the America kradic
参与项目的美国 kradic
decision-making process of the project
决策过程，
because they are capable they actively
因为他们有能力
working on the project so they have some
积极参与项目，所以他们有一些
understanding and they can
理解，他们可以
a contribution on the mailing lists as
在与邮件列表相关的邮件列表
it pertains to perhaps unimportant soft
中做出贡献 也许需要做出不重要的软
architecture decisions to be made and
决策，那就
that is there are lots and lots of best
是有很多很多的最佳实践
practices ideally it's a discussion with
，理想情况下这是一个带有
a conclusion based on the merits of the
结论基础的讨论 d 基于论证的优点，
argument where everyone on the end
最后每个人都
agrees yes that's the best solution and
同意，是的，这是最好的解决方案，
these discussions can be lengthy you
这些讨论可能很长，你
need to try to keep ego out and really
需要尽量保持自我，并真正
make sure it's not about the egos of the
确保它不是关于人们的自我，
people sometimes I'm easy but rather
有时我很容易但
it's about the technical content of the
而是关于问题的技术内容
question and the potential problem
和潜在的问题
solution now ideally you achieve
解决方案，现在理想情况下，您可以
consensus for people accustomed or the
为习惯的人或
ways companies do it these discussions
公司的做法达成共识。这些讨论
can be rather lengthy but again you
可能会相当冗长，但您
don't want say the project leader to
又不想说项目负责人
come down with a hammer because if they
得出一个 锤子，因为如果他们
do that too often people will leave so
经常这样做，人们会离开，所以
you need to tolerate you need to
你需要容忍你需要
tolerate lengthy discussions and hope
容忍冗长的讨论，并
that at the end everyone will be
希望最后每个人都会被
convinced or at least remain friendly
说服或至少保持友好
and supportive of the project because
和支持该项目，因为
that may take the series as a postal
这可能会将这个系列作为一个 邮政
address being told how the world is so
地址被告知世界如何如此
ideally there's consensus at the end if
理想，如果绝对没有共识让人们投票，那么最后就会
there absolutely is no consensus to be
达成共识，
had people vote it's a very
这是一种非常
idiosyncratic way of how decisions are
特殊的方式 如何做出决定
made some votes are cast to believe
一些投票人相信
shall we do this yes or no so people
我们是否应该
will go to +1 for agreement or a 0 for
with withholding or withdrawal and a
minus one affair that set against it now
if in such a world there is a - while
这样做 是 - 虽然
there is no veto right it might still be
没有否决权，但它仍然可能被
considered a veto because again you
视为否决权，因为你
really want what consensus so you dig
真的想要什么共识，所以你深入
into why is someone so dead-set that
研究为什么有人如此死心塌地以至于
they are not just silent but rather
他们不仅保持沉默，而是
explicitly argue this is not a good idea
明确地争辩这不是一个好主意
anyway I ultimately a decision has to be
无论如何，我最终必须做出决定，并且做出决定的
made and
way it's made is as mentioned before by
方式如前所述，通过
writing a summary email that goes Center
写一封摘要电子邮件将中心
data sent out of mailing lists where it
数据发送到邮件列表中，
can be read read widely and will also be
可以广泛阅读并且也将被
archived so that in the future you can
存档，以便将来您可以
reference that may email on the mailing
邮件列表存档中可能通过电子邮件发送的参考资料
list archive are for everyone to see so
供每个人查看，因此
let's take a look here at at some
让我们在这里看一下
numbers in an illustration really of
插图中的
some numbers in a well working
一些数字，这些数字实际上是一个运行良好
open-source project for every committee
的开源项目中的一些数字，适用于每个委员会
that may well be ten to a hundred
，可能是十到一个 一百个
contributors and also for each committee
贡献者，以及每个委员会
that may easily be ten thousands of
可能很容易拥有一万个
users so you can see how these are
用户，因此您可以看到这些是
orders of magnitudes difference between
differences between committees our
委员会之间差异之间的数量级差异我们的
project leaders contributors are
项目负责人贡献者是
developers and actual users hence
开发人员和实际用户，因此
deciding how to spend time to acquire
决定如何花时间获得
volunteers is not easy what if your what
志愿者不是 很容易，
if you're spending time on the wrong
如果你把时间花在错误的
people and it never pans out so you have
人身上并且永远不会成功，
to think about this as you go about it
那么你必须在做这件事时考虑这一点
and the right thing to realize is that
，正确的事情是要意识到
time is just gaseous resource and that
时间只是气态资源，
recruiting will take away from that time
招聘将需要 远离那段时间
that you could otherwise spend on
，否则你可以花在
developing the software so the best way
开发软件上，所以最好的方法
and this is how full bill costs it is to
，这就是将招聘视为一项投资的全部费用，这是
view recruiting as an investment it's a
time your investment and so you've got a
你的投资时间，所以你有一个
critically absorbent you make
批判性的吸收能力，你可以采取
incremental moves and you watch and
渐进式的行动 然后你观察和
review the feedback or the reactions you
审查你得到的反馈或反应，
get and based on that you incrementally
并在此基础上逐步
steer whether you invest more time I've
控制你是否投入更多时间我
gotta be open and welcoming in the
必须开放 并在一
beginning but you should not be spending
开始就欢迎，但你不应该花费
extra time unless you see how that
额外的时间，除非你看到那
person is willing to engage and willing
个人愿意参与并且愿意
and helpful here means
和乐于助人，这
that they read up on how you tell them
意味着他们阅读了你如何告诉他们
that they should be engaging with the
如果他们只是绊倒他们应该参与这个
project if they just stumble into the
项目 进入
forums ask questions in a poor way which
论坛以一种糟糕的方式提问，这
shows that they haven't read up on
表明他们没有阅读
anything it suggests that they're not
任何内容，这表明他们不是
particularly reliable and probably not
特别可靠，
that interested in the project if they
如果他们确实使用过这个项目，可能对项目没有那么感兴趣
did use and that little time figuring
，而且几乎没有时间
figuring out how it works and hence you
弄清楚它是如何使用的 工作，因此你
might just limit whatever time you're
可能只是限制你花在这些人身上的任何时间，
spending on these guys so view
所以将
recruiting as investment of your time
招聘视为你的时间投资
and walk with it so then any volunteer
并与它同行，这样任何
who is long enoug grew up with the
长期与该项目一起长大的志愿者
project will have loyalty to that
都会对该项目有忠诚度
project
has that investment in the project and
在项目中，
may ultimately and suddenly Webb gray
可能最终突然间韦伯·
has at its heart of the interests of the
格雷将项目利益置于其核心，
project and may ultimately become a
并可能最终
project leader themselves that's the
自己成为项目负责人，这是
step from a contributor to a committer
从合作伙伴迈出的一步 提交者的贡献者
and as a leader of the project they
和作为项目的领导者，他们
really need to show that by taking
确实需要通过承担
responsibility and that really like
责任来表明，真正像
leadership typically is is social walk
领导力一样通常是社交活动
of sorts so they need to if I hadn't
，所以如果我之前没有
done that before really be praising
这样做，他们需要真正表扬
other people providing positive social
其他人提供 积极的社会
feedback really making become helping
反馈真正让
the community feel whole and the people
社区感觉完整，人们
welcomed within that community the
在社区内受到欢迎
leaders here I'll only praise they
这里的领导者我只会称赞他们
acknowledge they provide credit etc they
承认他们提供了信用等，他们
may even go outside the project or say
甚至可能会离开项目，或者说
provide positive feedback about a
developer to their manager within
向他们的经理提供关于开发人员的积极反馈 在公司内部，
companies if that person is working on
如果该人
the project on company time or simply
在公司时间从事项目或只是
show give provide simple tokens of
展示 给予 提供简单的
appreciation it's amazing how far
感谢信 令人惊讶的是
t-shirts for example can go to keep
，例如 T 恤可以在多大程度上保持
people motivated
人们的积极性
contributing finally this five stages of
最后贡献
engagement that we are discussing are
我们正在讨论的这五个参与阶段是
some sort of basic career but then
一些 一种基本的职业，但
there's also the more elaborate career
还有
that I mentioned before that within the
我之前提到的更复杂的
community and within the foundation the
职业 社区和基金会内，
project leader will make that very
项目负责人将非常
explicit will give people a terminology
明确地为人们提供
on how to talk about the roles they have
有关如何谈论
a curious stages they are in etc and a
他们所处的好奇阶段等角色的术语，
critical part here of a project leaders
项目负责人
work is of course to determine whether
工作的关键部分当然是确定是否
the promotion of a regular contributor
有必要提拔
to a project leader or committee is
项目负责人或委员会的定期贡献者
warranted and that is one of the few
，这是少数
things that may not be done in public
可能不会在公开场合做的事情之一，
because it's so socially sensitive if
因为如果
someone's accepted for for committee
某人被接受担任委员会
post position then of course the
职位，这对社会非常敏感，那么
existing project leaders will have to
现有的项目负责人当然会 必须
make that very clear announce it visibly
非常清楚地宣布它
and welcome that person to the ranks of
并欢迎该人加入委员会的行列，
committee for their well-done continued
因为他们对项目的出色持续
contributions to the project alright so
贡献好吧，所以
we are not going to watch it in this
我们不会在本次讲座中观看它，
lecture but there is a very nice video
但那里有一个非常好的
out there on dealing with difficult
视频 与难相处的
people and open source projects called
人和开源项目打交道被称为
dealing with poisonous people because
与毒人打交道，因为
the wrong people in your project might
你项目中的错误人可能
really poison poison it and not only
真的会毒害pois 这样做，不仅
waste your time but really ruin ruin the
浪费你的时间，而且真的会毁了这个
project if they're smart and divisive
项目
whatever might be driving them you don't
have to assume that there's deliberate
mischief at work they're just not a good
match and thereby may be poisonous to
对项目有毒，
the project so the wrong people may be
所以错误的人可能会
wasting your time but might even split
浪费你的时间，但
the project if I've not stopped so this
如果我没有停止，甚至可能会拆分项目，所以这个
particular video suggests the four-step
特定的视频建议了四步
process for
过程，
you need to understand the poisonous
你需要了解有毒的
people come from and then identify them
人来自哪里，然后识别他们
since the best defense is being prepared
由于正在准备最好的防御措施，
you need to have your community if you
will be healthy so that there is no
因此如果您保持健康，就需要拥有自己的社区，这样对于
leverage point for anyone who
deliberately are not deliberately might
故意不
want to harm the community so building a
故意伤害社区的任何人都没有杠杆点，因此建立一个
healthy community is the main
健康的社区是主要的
preparatory measure and something you
准备措施和一些东西
want to do anyway so that goes
无论如何，您都想这样做，以便
hand-in-hand nicely part of that is
很好地携手并进，其中一部分
again
再次
public written archived complete and
公开书面存档
archived communication for all the
，所有
decisions are being documented so
决定的完整和存档通信都被记录在案 d 所以
leaving no room for conspiracy
没有为阴谋论留出空间
conspiracy theories so but let's assume
所以但是让我们
that now is a difficult person or
假设现在是一个难相处的人或
poisonous person how do you detect them
有毒的人 你如何
well simple things give them away like
很好地发现他们
they don't show respect they don't
actually read up on how the project
项目
wants people to behave because that's
希望人们表现出来，因为这是
their community rules and guidelines
他们的社区规则和准则，
because I clueless because they're
因为我一无所知，因为
already emotional etc they make sweeping
他们已经情绪化等等
claims they're probably lots of ways of
how you recognize someone doesn't
necessarily necessarily have to be a
but simply will be a difficult
person in this project in this context
在这种情况下，在这个项目中将是一个困难的人，
so dealing with them now is well one way
所以现在与他们打交道是一种很好的
of doing it with all a suddenly open
方式，所有突然的
source project have their share of
开源项目都有他们
experiences with trolls which is to not
与巨魔的经验，那就是不要
feed them an energy beast in the video
在视频中给他们喂食能量野兽
don't feed the troll I don't give them
'不要喂巨魔我不会
energy by responding to them rather than
通过回应他们来给他们能量，而不是
silently go away if you ignore if you
如果你忽略，如果你
absolutely they absolutely don't leave
绝对他们绝对不会离开
and somehow are able
并且以某种方式能够
- able to engage people and trigger
- abl  e 吸引人们并触发
people's hot buttons so that those
人们的热键，以便这些
people do respond and feed them well
人做出回应并很好地喂他们
apparently sometimes you can't help it
显然有时你无法帮助
but you have to boot them which means
但你必须启动他们，这意味着
you just remove them from the mailing
你只需将他们从邮件
lists and block them from disturbing the
列表中删除并阻止他们干扰
project communication and collaboration
项目 沟通和协作
all right so I walked you through these
都很好，所以我带你完成
five stages of open source volunteering
了开源志愿服务的这五个阶段，
where the volunteer initially a seeker
其中志愿者最初是一个寻求
visitor potential user for volunteer and
访问者，志愿者和
project leader really engages with the
项目负责人的潜在用户真正参与到
project and how the project needs to
项目中，以及项目需要如何
match the interests of the volunteer by
通过营销来匹配志愿者的兴趣
marketing explaining the project
解释
engaging with the volunteer working with
与与他们一起工作的志愿者参与的项目
them and and enabling a career for them
，并为他们创造职业生涯，
so that's that for this session we
这就是本次会议的内容，我们
looked at open source projects and
研究了开源项目和
community open source projects in
社区开源项目
general the project roles that people
，人们拥有的项目角色
have and the career stages that are
和可用的职业阶段
available to members of open source
开源
projects and then the three four five
项目成员再三四五
model of open project communities
模式开源项目社区
consisting of the three principles of
包括开放式沟通
local collaboration for practices of
实践的本地合作的三个原则
open communication and five stages of a
和一个
sauce volunteer that's it from me for
酱汁志愿者的五个阶段，这就是我
now thank you very much for your
现在的内容，非常感谢
attention and I see you in the next
您的关注，我们下期再见
session